



 

   //Questions array

   let questions = [

    {

         number:1,

         question: "The tripartite functions of school library includes these except",

         answer : "Examinations",

         options : [

                          "Community service",

                          "Learning",

                          "Examinations",

                          "Research"

                        ]

    

    },

    {

         number:2,

         question: "Presently most University libraries operate __",

         answer : "Hybrid library",

         options : [

                          "Digital library",

                          "Hybrid library",

                          "AI library",

                          "Manual library"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:3,

         question: "justifications for libraries include these except",

         answer : "Examinations",

         options : [

                          "Assignments",

                          "Examinations",

                          "Personal development",

                          "Research"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:4,

         question: "__ has to do with enquiry into the unknown",

         answer : "Research",

         options : [

                          "Reading",

                          "Learning",

                          "Assignment",

                          "Research"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:5,

         question: "Information resources in the library include the following except",

         answer : "Business correspondence",

         options : [

                          "Government publications",

                          "Business correspondence",

                          "Reference information resources",

                          "Library catalogue"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:6,

         question: "___ is a systematic listing of materials in the library",

         answer : "Catalogue",

         options : [

                          "Gazettes",

                          "Catalogue",

                          "Journals",

                          "Serials"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:7,

         question: "___ resources provide information on persons",

         answer : "Biographical reference",

         options : [

                          "Encyclopedias",

                          "Directories",

                          "Reference resources",

                          "Biographical reference"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:8,

         question: "___are usually consulted for specific information Reference",

         answer : "Reference resources",

         options : [

                          "Reference resources",

                          "Encyclopedias",

                          "Directories",

                          "Biological references"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:9,

         question: "___ are the most consulted the",

         answer : "",

         options : [

                          "reference books",

                          "Directories",

                          "Encyclopedias",

                          "Bibliographies Yearbooks"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:10,

         question: "__ The first step to a successful research is",

         answer : "Knowledge of resources to look at",

         options : [

                          "Knowledge of resources to look at",

                          "A well defined purpose",

                          "Preconceived idea of subject matter",

                          "Access to necessary materials"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:11,

         question: "___ are the most prolific publishers",

         answer : "Government publications",

         options : [

                          "Journals periodicals",

                          "Serial publications",

                          "Government publications",

                          "Electronic information resources"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:12,

         question: "Classifications of government publications include these except",

         answer : "Institutional repositories",

         options : [

                          "Institutional repositories",

                          "Research documents for specialists",

                          "Records of government administration",

                          "Popular sources of information"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:13,

         question: "The most detailed records that supports most scientific, legal and historic studies are found in",

         answer : "Serial publications",

         options : [

                          "Journals periodicals",

                          "Government publications",

                          "Electronic information resources",

                          "Serial publications"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:14,

         question: "The essence of newspapers is its",

         answer : "Timelessness",

         options : [

                          "Timelessness",

                          "Details",

                          "Directory function",

                          "Degree of Information"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:15,

         question: "__ is a publication in any medium issued in successive parts bearing numerical or chronological designations and intended to be continued indefinitely",

         answer : "Serials",

         options : [

                          "Directories",

                          "Serials",

                          "Yearbooks",

                          "Catalogue"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:16,

         question: "The most important part of science and technology libraries is",

         answer : "Periodicals",

         options : [

                          "Journals",

                          "Institutional repositories",

                          "Periodicals",

                          "Serials"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:17,

         question: "___ are usually 5 years ahead of books in every subject",

         answer : "Journals",

         options : [

                          "Institutional repositories",

                          "Periodicals",

                          "Journals",

                          "Directories"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:18,

         question: "__ constitute the backbone of the research collection",

         answer : "Serials",

         options : [

                          "Periodicals",

                          "Institutional repositories",

                          "Journals",

                          "Serials"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:19,

         question: "Electronic information resources include these except",

         answer : "Serial publications",

         options : [

                          "Online public access catalogue",

                          "Online databases",

                          "Institutional repositories",

                          "Serial publications"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:20,

         question: "___ are one of the best sources of critical analysis of any decision usually found in law reviews",

         answer : "Case notes",

         options : [

                          "Case notes",

                          "Technical reports",

                          "Special collections",

                          "Memoirs"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:21,

         question: "Scientists hold which of these in high esteem",

         answer : "Technical reports",

         options : [

                          "Special collections",

                          "Memoirs",

                          "Technical reports",

                          "Case notes"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:22,

         question: "___ houses electronic information resources generated within the institutions",

         answer : "Institutional repositories",

         options : [

                          "Serial publications",

                          "Online public access catalogue",

                          "Online databases",

                          "Institutional repositories"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:23,

         question: "___are means of informing the reading public on what have been published in a particular field",

         answer : "Abstract",

         options : [

                          "Index",

                          "Abstract",

                          "Gazettes",

                          "Guide books"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:24,

         question: "___ is a systematically arranged list of materials given enough information about each item to make it easy to be found",

         answer : "Index",

         options : [

                          "Index",

                          "Gazettes",

                          "Guide books",

                          "Abstract"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:25,

         question: "___ contains bibliographic information of a library",

         answer : "Online public access catalogue",

         options : [

                          "Serial publications",

                          "Institutional repositories",

                          "Online public access catalogue",

                          "Online databases"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:26,

         question: "The most logical place to start searching for a book in a library is",

         answer : "Catalogue",

         options : [

                          "Serials",

                          "Directories",

                          "Catalogue",

                          "Yearbooks"  

                          ]

    

    }

     ];   